The database of each dictionary (U8 file) is often updated thanks to modifications

provided by different users.


You can download it for each language, the links below will download a ZIP file from

which you have to extract the U8 file (*.u8). However some of these links are no longer

valid and have been disabled.


You have then to convert the U8 file to XML format (File -> XML conversion) and to

replace the former XML file by the new one you created in HanYuDic\Data.

WARNING: Be careful to put this file in the right folder and to give it the correct name

(its name must be the same as the one of the former XML file)

IMPORTANT: The file format has changed for the database CFDict and the new updates

for the Chinese/French dictionary are no longer suitable with this application.